(Sheldon:)Isn't that a little juvenile?
(Amy:)More juvenile than this?
(Sheldon:)I'll get the blankets.
(Sheldon:)You Google how
to have childlike fun.
(Sheldon:)You know what,
I'm being a bad host.
(Howard:)Let me get some more coffee.
(Bernadette:)Oh, let me do it, Howard.
No, I got it.
(Bernadette:)So, Josh, what do you do?
(Josh:)I'm studying oceanography
down in San Diego.
(Bernadette:)Oh, how nice.
I loved Finding Nemo.
(Raj:)Enough chitchat.
(Raj:)How do we know you are
who you say you are?
(Josh:)Why would I lie?
(Raj:)Okay, you got me there.
(Raj:)You here looking for money?
No.
(Raj:)A kidney, cornea,
piece of his liver?
(Howard:)No.
(Raj:)You're in a Beatles cover band
(Raj:)and you need Howard to replace
your dad as Ringo.
(Bernadette:)Why don't you help
with the coffee?
(Raj:)Okay, but something
smells fishy.